[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Now, neural networks provide some exciting results, however,
现在 神经网络提供了一些非常振奋人心的结果
they do come with some challenges.
但是它们也确实面临着很多挑战
So, on the pro side, they really enable you to represent this non-linear
好的一面是它们让我们可以真正的表征非线性的
complex features and they have impressive results,
复杂的特征并且具有令人印象深刻的好的性能
not just in computer vision, but in some other areas like speech recognition.
不仅仅是在计算机视觉领域 在其他领域比如语音识别也同样有效
So systems like Siri on the phone and others use the neural
所以像Siri和其他一些系统
networks behind the scene, as well as some text analysis tasks.
都使用神经网络 另外一些文本分析任务也用了到神经网络
And its potential for much more impact in the wide range of areas.
神经网络有潜力在很广泛的领域造成重要影响
Now they do come with some challenges.
但也面临一些挑战
And to understand those challenges,
为了更好的理解这些挑战
we need to talk about the workflow of training a neural network.
我们需要介绍训练神经网络的工作流
So you need to start with lots and lots and lots of data.
在一开始我们需要大量的数据
And that data has to be labeled.
并且这些数据都得是标注数据
Every image has to have, what dog was in the image, is it a labrador,
每个图片必须指明是包含哪一种狗 是拉布拉多?
is it a poodle, is it a golden retriever, chihuahua and so on.
是狮子狗? 是金毛还是吉娃娃?
And that requires a lot of human annotation and that can be hard.
但是这需要大量的人工标注 可能非常困难
But we start to [INAUDIBLE] some of the images.
然后我们开始 输入一些图片
We feed it, we split them into training tasks or validation sets as we discussed,
把它们划分为训练和测试数据集
and we learned that deep neural network, and that can take quite a while.
然后我们训练一个深度神经网络 可能得花一些时间
But once we validate, we realize that that complex eight layer structure of
但是验证过后 我们意识到复杂的八层结构
60 million parameters wasn't exactly what we needed and
包含6,000万参数的模型并不是我们想要的
we need to revise it, or we need to adjust parameters or change how we learn it.
我们需要修改一下模型 或者调整一下参数 亦或者改变一下学习方法
And we have to iterate again and again and again.
然后我们需要不停的迭代这个过程
And in fact, to get that winning neural network, the one,
事实上 为了得到那个能取胜的神经网络
they really needed to connect various layers with different representations and
他们必须联接很多代表不同特征的层
lots of complexes in the learning algorithm, so that was hard.
和很多复杂的细节 所以说其实非常困难
So although there's some great pros, neural networks,
所以尽管神经网络有一些非常明显的优点
they also come with some cons too.
它们也有缺点
They require lots of data to get great performance, they're computationally
它们需要大量的数据来获得良好的性能 它们计算量大
expensive, even with GPUs they can be computationally expensive.
尽管可以使用GPU加速 但是计算量仍然偏大
And they're extremely hard to tune, so you have a lot of choices, the more layers
而且它们很难进行调优 你有太多的选择
you use, how many layers or parameters you use and that can be really hard.
你用的层数越多 关于层数和参数多少的选择就越复杂
So if you combine the computational choices and costs with so
所以如果你仓促的把过多的选择和计算开销 搅在一起
many things too soon, you end up with an incredibly hard process for
你会发现很难搞清楚
figuring out what neural network to use.
到底哪个神经网络比较适用
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community